Yahor Paulovich



Unity Developer

Game Developer

 $\circ \circ \circ$



SUMMARY

I specialize in writing clean code architecture using DI, applying design patterns, and implementing various gameplay mechanics using entity component system.

Open to work remotely anywhere and on-site or hybrid in Warsaw, Poland. I have a work permit in Poland and considering both B2B and full-time employment.

I love to solve complicated problems in a simple and beautiful way and by giving a problem to me you can be sure I found a creative solution for it!

PORTFOLIO



https://yahorpaulovich.github.io/Portfolio



https://github.com/YahorPaulovich



https://yahor-paulovich.itch.io







CONTACTS

+48 728 377 407



yahorpaulovich

@Yahor_Paulovich

live:.cid.c78181f6e842ded6

Pogodna Bialystok, 15-354, Poland

LANGUAGES

EN B1+ BY Native ы

UA

RU

I have no problem reading technical documentation, but I still need to improve my English



EXPERIENCE



Unity Developer Jan 2024 - Present · 5 mos

Hype Games FZE LLC · Seasonal

Dubai, United Arab Emirates · Remote

I was doing Action and Casual game development and prototyping.

Skills: C# · Unity · Zenject · WebGL.



Middle Unity Developer Feb 2024 - Mar 2024 · 2 mos

Voidverse Studios · Full-time Toronto, Ontario, Canada · Remote

It was a contract job and I was working on an unannounced mobile project.

Skills: C# · Unity · Zenject · Mobile Application Development.



Unity Developer Oct 2023 - Jan 2024 · 4 mos

Extension Forces · Seasonal

Buenos Aires, Argentina · Remote

I was doing simulator game development and Xreal Light MR/VR/AR prototyping.

Skills: C# · Unity · Virtual Reality (VR) · Augmented Reality (AR) · Mixed Reality (MR) · Zenject.



Unity Developer Jan 2023 - Apr 2023 · 4 mos

Gamedev Camp · Seasonal

Vilniaus, Lithuania · Remote

As the lead programmer, I worked with my team on Run Over It, a survival tower defense game. I developed a horde spawn system and managed to reduce the load in the game to a minimum. This way the player gets an infinite adventure in addition to the story mode while maintaining immersion.

 $\textbf{Skills:} \ \texttt{C\#} \cdot \texttt{Unity} \cdot \texttt{Unity's Data-Oriented Technology Stack} \cdot \texttt{Gameplay Programming} \cdot \texttt{Software}$ Development English.



Unity Developer Sep 2022 - Present · 1 yrs 9 mos

GU Solutions · Self-employed Białystok, Podlaskie, Poland · On-site

Collaborated with b2b clients to prototype Action, Adventure, and Indie games, fostering success on various platforms.

Skills: C# \cdot Unity \cdot URP Custom Renderer Features \cdot Multithreaded Programming \cdot DOTS \cdot Animation Rigging \cdot Gameplay Programming \cdot Software Development \cdot Zenject \cdot Hyper Casual Game Development · ML-Agents.



Unity Developer Jul 2021 - Jul 2022 · 1 yr 1 mo

Gammister · Full-time

Dubai, United Arab Emirates · Remote

It was a contract job and I spearheaded the development of a gambling project, guiding it from initial concept to a fully realized prototype, and successfully overseeing its beta testing phase on the Google Play Store. This intricate and innovative project provided me with invaluable learning opportunities.

Skills: C# · Unity · ASP.NET Core SignalR · ASP.NET Entity Framework Core · Microsoft SQL Server · Docker · Ubuntu Server 20.04 LTS · Git · Postman · Android · Mobile Application ${\tt Development} \cdot {\tt Problem \ Solving} \cdot {\tt Software \ Design \ Patterns} \cdot {\tt OOP.}$

HARD SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C#
Game Engine: Unity

Platforms: Android, PC, WebGL and Pico VR

VCS

Git

NETWORKING

Mirror Networking, Netcode for GameObjects

NON-RDBMS

Firebase Database

ARCHITECTURAL SKILLS

In OOP style, I can design Clean, Onion, Hexagonal and Data Driven Architecture

PACKAGES

UI, Tilemap, Animations, Timeline, Animation Rigging, Cinemachine, Physics, New Input System, AI Navigation, Audio, Localization, Addressables, URP Renderer Features, Shader Graph, Visual Effect Graph, Particle System, IAP,

PLUGINS

DOTween, Google Play Games, A* Pathfinding Project Pro, Agents Navigation, Amplify Shader Editor, FMOD for Unity

SDKs

PicoVR Unity SDK, GameAnalytics, AppsFlyer, OneSignal SDK

LIBRARIES

Zenject, VContainer, UniTask, Newtonsoft.Json

DATA-ORIENTED TECHNOLOGY STACK

ECS for Unity, Burst Compiler, C# Job System LeoEcsLite, Morpeh

OTHER SKILLS

LANGUAGES

C#/.NET, C++, Java

ORM

—

Microsoft ASP.NET Entity Framework Core

RDBMS

Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, MariaDB

NETWORKING

Protocols: TCP, UDP, WebSockets, WebRTC
Libraries: Microsoft ASP.NET Core SignalR
Server OS: Ubuntu Linux Server, Windows Server

PAAS: Docker

Cloud Platforms: Microsoft Azure, Digital Ocean, Google Cloud Platform

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering

International University MITSO 2018 - 2022

Information Systems and Technologies (In Economics) GPA: 3.8

The main disciplines studied were: Web design and design patterns; System analysis and design of information systems (with a web application development module); Scripting programming languages; Computer networks; Applied data processing systems; Algorithmization and programming; Programming network applications; Object-oriented design and programming; Distributed information systems; Probability theory and mathematical statistics; Software development technologies;

Skills: Software Engineering · Software Development · Mobile Applications · C# · .NET Core · C++ · OOP · Software Design Patterns · Microsoft SQL Server · Transact-SQL (T-SQL) · Microsoft Foundation Class (MFC) · Android Studio · JavaSE · JavaServer Pages (JSP) · MySQL · Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) · Java Swing · HTML5 · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · JavaScript · TypeScript · NumPy · Pandas · Node.js · Express.js

... BOOKSHELF















